mojosavings.com 2016-12-29

# Privacy Policy & Disclosure

**Privacy Policy for www.mojosavings.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at mojosavings@gmail.com.

At www.mojosavings.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.mojosavings.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.mojosavings.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.mojosavings.com does not use cookies.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.mojosavings.com.

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.mojosavings.com and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….  
Google Adsense

Commission Junction

Escalate Media Network

Linkshare

My Savings

Logical Media

Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.mojosavings.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.mojosavings.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.mojosavings.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Disclosure**

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by Mike and Lisa. This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

The compensation received will never influence the content, topics or posts made in this blog. All advertising is in the form of advertisements generated by a third party ad network. Those advertisements will be identified as paid advertisements.

The owner(s) of this blog is not compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the blog owners. If we claim or appear to be experts on a certain topic or product or service area, we will only endorse products or services that we believe, based on our expertise, are worthy of such endorsement. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

All prices contained in the posts are current at the time of the post. Mojo Savings is not responsible for typos on other sites, errors or omissions on other companies sites, or if the pirce changes after the post is posted.

**Material Connection Disclosure**

Unless otherwise expressly stated, you should assume that Mojo Savings has an affiliate relationship or other material connection to the providers of goods and services mentioned by, recommended, hyperlinked to, or otherwise referenced on Mojo Savings. In addition, you should assume that Mojo Savings may be compensated monetarily or non-monetarily when you visit, purchase goods or services from, or take any other action on a third-party website mentioned by, recommended, hyperlinked to, or otherwise referenced on Mojo Savings. You should always perform due diligence before buying any goods or services online or offline.

Follow Us On: [Mojo's Facebook ](https://www.facebook.com/mojosavings), [Instagram](https://instagram.com/mojosavings/), [Twitter](https://twitter.com/MoJoSavings) and [Pinterest](http://pinterest.com/mojosavings/) and catch all our deals!
